You must pray, to God and ask, what you want.
Musicie się modlić do Boga i prosić o to czego chcecie.
Ask for: Complete satisfaction in my heart, joy in my heart, bliss in my heart, so that
Proście o "Pełne zadowolenie w moim sercu, radość w moim sercu, błogość w moim sercu tak, że
the whole world becomes blissful.
cały świat staje się pełen błogości.
Give me love, love that I could… love the whole world and that the whole world becomes
Daj mi miłość, miłość tak żebym mógł kochać cały świat i cały świat zjednoczył się
one in love.
w miłości.
Give salvation to this… humanity.
Daj wyzwolenie tej ludzkości,
Which is suffering.
która cierpi.
Take me to Your feet.
Weź mnie do swych stóp.
Cleanse me with Thy love.
Oczyść mnie Twoją miłością.
Now see if there is God or not?
Teraz zobaczmy czy jest Bóg czy nie?
You can feel it within yourself.
Możecie to poczuć w sobie.
He hears you.
On was słyszy.
He understands you.
On was rozumie.
He’s the glory of all the glory.
On jest chwałą wszelkiej chwały.
He loves you.
On was kocha.
He protects you.
On was chroni.
He guides you.
On was prowadzi.
He created you to reveal His love, but accept it.
On was stworzył by ukazać swą miłość tylko ją przyjmijcie.
Any time any thought is coming you pray and you will be moving in the waves of that ocean
Kiedykolwiek, jakakolwiek myśl przychodzi, wy się modlicie i będziecie poruszać się na falach tego oceanu,
which is unconscious mind, which starts with thoughtless awareness.
którym jest nieświadomy umysł, który zaczyna się wraz ze świadomością bez myśli.
If you cannot become thoughtless, you pray to Him: “Forgive me for what I
Jeżeli nie możecie osiągnąć stanu bez myśli, modlicie się do Niego: "Wybacz mi
have done and forgive those who have done harm to me.
za to co zrobiłem i wybacz tym, którzy wyrządzili mi krzywdę.